export default [
  {
    question:
      "Who played Paul Atreides in David Lynch's 1984 adaptation of Dune?",
    answer: "Kyle MacLachlan",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who plays Paul Atreides in the not yet released adaptaion of Dune?",
    answer: "TimothÃ©e Chalamet",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is your favorite actor in the 1984 movie Dune?",
    answer: "Sting, but we'll also accept Sir Patrick Stewart",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question: "What movie did David Lynch pass on directing in favor of Dune?",
    answer: "Return of the Jedi",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the director of the new Dune?",
    answer: "Denis Villeneuve",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the material being mined on Arrakis?",
    answer: "The Spice Melange",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question: "What do the fremen do with their dead?",
    answer: "Render them down for their water",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the exclusive religious and mystical sisterhood in Dune?",
    answer: "The Bene Gesserit",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a muad'dib?",
    answer: "a type of desert mouse",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
  {
    question: "What is melange made of?",
    answer: "sandworms",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a crysknife made of?",
    answer: "a sandworm's tooth",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Paul's tribal name among the Fremen?",
    answer: "Usal",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the last thing Paul must do before he is accepted as a full Fremen?",
    answer: "Ride a sandworm",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the needle tipped with poison called",
    answer: "Gom gabbar",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Paul's son named?",
    answer: "Leto",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Leto become far into the future in the books of Dune?",
    answer: "A sandworm",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the baron's grandson?",
    answer: "Paul Atreides",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the emperor's truthsayer?",
    answer: "The Reverend Mother Mohiam",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
  {
    question: "Which Fremen leader does Paul form a close relationship?",
    answer: "Stilgar",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
  {
    question: "What color are Fremen eyes?",
    answer: "all blue, including the sclera",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Chani's father?",
    answer: "Dr. Kynes",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
  {
    question: "Mentats are trained to be like what?",
    answer: "computers",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    question: "How can you spot a mentat?",
    answer: "Their lips are stained red from sapho juice",
    answerShown: false,
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
].map((q, index) => ({ ...q, id: index + 1 }));
